RF were first invented by Russian spy Harry Stockman, even though radio frequency identification or
RFID for short is largely unknown in public.
It is being currently used by Walmart, McDonald's, Amazon and even American Army.
There are endless industries in which RFID can play an important part.
So in this course, we are going to see how to program RFID tags.
We will start this course by understanding what RFID is.
Then we will program RFID, mifare classic cards using one, two, two, in which we will see what are
data blocks, what are value blocks and sector trailer.
Then we will program the same card using eight microcontroller.
After learning how to program RFID tags, we will see the security of RFID cards and we will start with
offensive security and try to crack RFID tags using prox mark three.
We will see how to crack Mifare cards without knowing the actual key.
We will also see how to clone Mifare cards on magic cards.
Then we will look how to make RFID cards fully secure and how to overcome such type of attacks.
At the end, we are also going to do a real world practical example of RFID tags with correct market
standards.
Thank you.